[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Can you hear me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "You're back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "CD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "How long was it before he finally told you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "I think it was a week or two, as I remember.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Where do you feel you get the strength to be like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Well, first of all, I'm almost 74.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "I'm serious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "If I could replay a moment for you now, what would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Oh, my goodness, my husband telling me that he thought we should adopt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Valerie, how -- finally, how would you like to be remembered?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", ":", "RB", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Oh, that's great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mohammad Atta"], "LOCATION": ["Boston"]}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Well, because in Boston, Mohammad Atta and nine other al Qaeda hijacked two planes back in 9/11.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Who needs to have a knife in mid-air anyway?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "The question is what can destroy an airplane.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Mary Schiavo, am I missing something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Yes, you actually can kill and bring down a plane with a knife.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Schiavo"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 467, "question": "How do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "The threat is -- because they will be shot dead by federal air marshals or, you know --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Just to clarify, there is a federal marshal aboard every single domestic flight in America, is there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["TSA"]}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ":", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "How do you know they are going to shoot them dead if they are not an board?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Because look -- look at it from the TSA's point of view, which is there is a real threat of bombs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Why are you so confident it's not going to happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Because the level of security is just night and day from before 9/11 to today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Am I missing something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Lino, what do people feel about that down there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Well, you are probably not surprised to hear, we are not for sexual abuse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "And what do you think may happen here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "(inaudible) fact.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "What about an assault weapons ban?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Assault weapons ban, there is very little support for assault weapons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "When the new Pope is in play, what should they be thinking to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Look, this is about something very holy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "What is the way through this impasse, particularly in getting a proper budget deal done, proper debt deal done, making sure the America is the focal point of how we move forward here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "President Obama knows this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Has Lance Armstrong got that kind of chance, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "Well, a bit of a disclosure.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lance Armstrong"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130312pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "But is it a possibility?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]